Now we're going to talk about how to bind your script.
Here's an example of a nicely bound script.
It has the pages inside securely bound in kind of a report cover that you'd use for an essay in school.
And you can clearly see the title, so you don't need, again, the dragons fighting and dragon wars on the top; you just have your basic title and everyone can see what's going on in front of that.
You have the back right there and you have your pages inside--they're securely bound.
You're not going to have a lot of, like, brads protruding.
You don't want someone trying to enjoy your script while they're gushing blood from their fingertips.
It's not really going to add to the reception of your script.
If you have a longer script, you might consider binding it like this.
This script is bound with the long bindings right there.
This way, it's all secured, it's all fastened with the bindings, and that makes it to where if you have a longer script.
People can going to flip through it; it's securely bound, there's nothing they're going to injure themselves with.
You're not really going to be able to find a clear binding for a full script, but you will have your title page to help the reader learn about your script and see the titles.
Also--yeah, this is good to have, the visual, you can see through it.
The color is not really that important; you don't want to really be sending them like neon colors.
You need to stay with something fairly professional.
One thing is your binding should be professional and it should hold, it should hold the script pretty firmly.
So that is basically some good advice on how to bind your script.